练习 1-32：名词和动词的规则转换。在下面的列表中，把
Exercise 1-32 Regular Transitions of Nouns and Verbs In the list below, change the
名词的重音从第一个音节移到动词的第二个音节。这是
stress from the first syllable for nouns to the second syllable for verbs. This is
一种规则且一致的变化。语调非常有力量，你会注意到当
a regular, consistent change. Intonation is so powerful that you'll notice when the
重音改变时，元音发音也会跟着变。下面开始词表：
stress changes, the pronunciation of the vowels does too. An accent to accent, a
concert to concert a conflict to conflict a contest to contest a contract to
contract a contrast to contrast a convert to convert a convict to convict a default
to default, a desert to desert, a discharge to discharge, an envelope to
envelop, an incline to incline, an influence to influence, an insert to
insert, an insult to insult, An object to object, perfect to perfect, a permit to
permit, a present to present, produce to produce, progress to progress, a project
to project, a pronoun to pronounce, a protest a rebel to rebel, a recall to
recall, a record to record, a reject to reject, research to research, a subject to
subject, a survey to survey, a suspect to suspect.